{
    "question": "Bedanya pemakaian because sama because of itu apa ya?\u00a0",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "because itu bukannya karena, kalau because of = sebab.. misalnya because of it,... sebab itu... kalau keliru maaf ya kak <br>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "<span>- because adalah kata sambung, dan diikuti oleh &#039;subyek&#039; beserta &#039;kata kerja&#039;. misal: He can&#039;t go to the party because he feels sick.\u00a0</span><br><span>perhatikan bahwa &#039;because&#039; langsung diikuti &#039;he&#039; sebagai subyek dan &#039;feels&#039; sebagai kata kerja.\u00a0</span><br><span>- because of adalah kata depan, karenanya diikuti dengan kata/frasa benda atau kata kerja bentuk -ing. misal: He can&#039;t go to the party because of his sickness. atau: He can&#039;t go to the party because of feeling sick.</span><br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "tolong-jelaskan-secara-singkat-dan-jelas-pengertian-dari-report-t-269",
            "question": "Tolong jelaskan secara singkat dan jelas pengertian dari report teks",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Definition of Report<br>Report is a text which presents information about something, as it is. It is as a result of systematic observation and analysis<br><br>Generic Structure of Report<br>1. General classification: Stating classification of general aspect of thing; animal, public place, plant, etc which will be discussed in general<br>2. Description: Describing the thing which will be discussed in detail; part per part , customs or deed for living creature and usage for materials<br><br>Language Feature of Report<br>\u2022 Introducing group or general aspect<br>\u2022 Using conditional logical connection; when, so, etc<br><span>\u2022 Using simple present tense</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "report text adalah salah satu jenis teks yang masuk kategori \" factual text \"<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "jelasin-tentang-present-perfect-tense-920",
            "question": "Jelasin tentang present perfect tense\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Present perfect adalah tenses yang menyatakan bahwa kejadian sudah dilakukan.<br>Rumus : S + Have/Has(Auxiliary) + V3<br>Misal : I have done my homework<br>Unsur : I = Subject<br>Have = Aux/Have/Has<br>Done = V3<br>Homework = Object<br>Umumnya ditambahkan kata Since + Time<br>Jadi : I have done my homework since this morning<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "present perfect itu berhubungan dengan kejadian yang sudah selesai. kata kuncinya sih ada kata \"sudah\", \"baru saja\", dsb.<br><br>misalkan \"saya sudah mengerjakan PR\", atau i have done my homework<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "combine-the-sentences-using-too-so-or-either-and-neither-1-d-745",
            "question": "Combine the sentences using : Too, so, or either and neither    1. Dogs\u00a0can't eat vegetables. Cats can't eat vegetables\r\n2. We haven't eaten yet. Father hasn't yet\r\n3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not seventeen years old\r\n\r\nJawabannya yang Jelas ya :)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. Dogs can&#039;t eat vegetables. Neither can cats<br>2. We haven&#039;t eaten yet. Father hasn&#039;t either<br>3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not either<br><br>setau aku begitu aja sih udah betul. mudah-mudahan membantu ya:)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-bahasa-inggris-dia-mengernyitkan-alisnya-547",
            "question": "Apa bahasa Inggris dia mengernyitkan alisnya?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "he furrowed his brow",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-the-word-darling-is-derived-from-an-old-english-term-meaning-251",
            "question": "1. The word \"Darling\" is derived from an old english term meaning \"Favorite Minion\" . Explain the positive and negative meaning of \"Darling\".    2. IBM is has laid of 20 percent of their workforce with a signature on a single piece of paper.\r\n\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 1\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 2\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 3\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 4\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 5\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 6\r\na. Find out the error option.\r\nb. Explain why it is wrong\r\n\r\nmohon bantuannya yaa..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. The word \"Darling\" is derived from an old English term meaning \"Favorite Minion\" . Explain the positive and negative meaning of \"Darling\".<br>Positive Meaning : It&#039;s a person that we concern as lovely and lovable, therefore we prioritize this darling as the first priority.<br>Negative : Since the word darling means favorite minion, it also trigger the feeling of possessiveness, that sometime it has negative effect on their freedom and privacy.\u00a0<br><br><span>2.\u00a0</span><u>IBM</u><span>\u00a0is\u00a0</span><u>has</u><span>\u00a0laid of\u00a0</span><u>20 percent</u><span>\u00a0of\u00a0</span><u>their</u>\u00a0<u>workforce</u><span>\u00a0with a signature on a\u00a0</span><u>single</u><span>\u00a0piece of paper.</span><br>\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 1\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 2\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 3\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 4\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 5\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 6<br>a. Find out the error option.<br><br>number 2 - &gt; should be<br>IBM has laid without &#039;is&#039;\u00a0<br>b. Explain why it is wrong<br>if we use Is, then it will have pasive meaning, which means that IBM get bankrupt due to their worker\u00a0<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-dari-dialog-bergaining-987",
            "question": "Contoh dari dialog bergaining?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "In a traditional market there are two friends named Rifky and Obet. They are looking for goldfish, they are going to make a party at Rifky\u2019s house by roasting goldfish.<br><span>Rifky:\u00a0we should buy cheaper goldfish because our money is not much<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0sure, that\u2019s why we have to round to get the cheaper price<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0but I\u2019m tired..we have rounded the whole part of this market but the price of all goldfish is almost the same<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0Look at there\u2026! There\u2019s a goldfish Fishmonger that we have not been there yet<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0ok, come on<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0what the price of this goldfish in a kilo?</span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0It\u2019s 27.000 rupiahs a kilo<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0That\u2019s too expensive,\u00a0\u00a0may I bargain?</span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0How much can you pay, boys?<br></span><span>Obet: what about 20.000 rupiahs a kilo?<br></span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0sorry I can\u2019t. it\u2019s a local goldfish, taken from ponds around this area<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0\u00a0give me a break\u2026you must decrease the price. You said that we may bargain.<br></span><span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0I&#039;ll make a special price for you, boys.</span>\u00a025.000 rupiahs a kilo. What about that?<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0I don\u2019t think so, give me 22.000 rupiahs a kilo and we\u2019ll take 3 kilos<br></span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0I\u2019m loss..I have no profit if I sell with that price. Just for you boys I give you 22.500 rupiahs per kilo but you have to buy 4 kilos. Do you agree?<br></span><span>Rifky:give us for second please.<br></span>RIFKY WISPERING OBET<br><span>Rifky: \u00a0 it\u2019s cheaper among all the goldfish Fishmonger that we have visited. Should we take it?<br></span><span>Obet: yes I know\u2026ok we just take it<br></span><span>Rifky: Ok, we\u2019ll take 4 kilos for 22.500 rupiahs<br></span><span>Fishmonger: that\u2019s a wise buyer\u2026here\u2019s the fish boy. I hope you feel satisfied.<br></span><span>Rifky and Obet: thank you</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-text-hartatory-explenation-yang-berjudul-effect-of-insomni-716",
            "question": "Buat text hartatory explenation \u00a0yang berjudul effect of insomnia",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Effect of Insomnia<br>Horatory -&gt; thesis -&gt; reason -&gt; suggestion<br><br>Insomnia is kind of illness that makes people hard to sleep. Due to its negative effect, this illness is categorized as the dangerous symptoms. The reason could be classified from Internal feelings of the person. Therefore if we have this illness, better to have consultation toward the doctor. We stand to benefit by the greater time of sleep that we have.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ada-yang-tau-gak-cara-menjawab-soal-bahasa-inggris-un-sma-dengan-902",
            "question": "Ada yang tau gak cara menjawab soal Bahasa Inggris UN SMA dengan trik tertentu supaya cepat dalam mengerjakannya.?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "kalau mau mengerjakan soal bhs inggris dengan mudah ya kalu bisa tau artinya soal bhs inggris itu pasti tau jawabanya.....<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Perbanyak vocabulary, sering-sering ngelakuin latihan listening karena 20 soal pertama di UN SMA ngegunain metode ini. Perbanyak baca modul buat ngebantu. Ngulang soal yang sudah dikerjain. Dan terakhir do&#039;a minta kemudahan",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "arrange-the-jumbled-words-to-form-meaningful-sentencesstarting-w-193",
            "question": "arrange the jumbled words to form meaningful sentences,starting with the underlined words. 1. phone-puppet-his-invite-the-I-number-my-see-Finto-know-will-if-show-to-I-at-place 2. and-holiday-Bali-if-have-will-his-Lombok-long-go-year-Mr. Kukuh-family-to-they-and-this-a \u00a0 mohon di bantu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "2. Mr. Kukuh and his family will go to Bali and Lombok if they have a long holiday this year<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "make-good-dialogues-expressing-feeling-and-attitude-based-on-the-373",
            "question": "Make good dialogues expressing feeling and attitude based on the following situations??    Hendra has a conversation with his mother in the evening. He tells her that he saw two black long plastic bags. He tought they were rubbish bags. When he came nearer, they were actually the corpse bags.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Mother: Good evening, Hendra<br>Hendra: Good evening, mom<br>Mother: Where have you been?<br>Hendra: I went to Ani&#039;s room to study together<br>Mother: Nice! Good boy..<br>Hendra: Umm...Mom, i have something to tell you<br>Mother: What is it?<br>Hendra: When on my way home, i saw a long and black plastic bag. I thought it&#039;s a rubbish bag. But when i came nearer the plastic bag, i smell a disgusting smell. So i open the plastic bag, and there&#039;s a corpse inside it! I was shocked, mom<br>Mother: Did you report it to the police?<br>Hendra: I have<br>Mother: Good boy, now\u00a0  let&#039;s have dinner<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "mom: Welcome home darling! how was school?<br>hendra: well, if i have to be honest... not that good...<br>mom:\u00a0what happen hendra? come, take a seat and lets talk about this.<br>hendra: okay mom...<br>mom: so, tell me exactly what happen<br>hendra: when i was riding home with my motorcycle, i saw 2 black long plastic bags. i actually thought they were rubbish bag but when i came near it, they were actually bags full of corpse. i was so shocked earlier.<br>mom: my my... did u call the police?<br>hendra: yes i did mom, the policeman said that i did the right thing to call the police<br>mom: now thats my boy!\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}